## **BOY SUGIJAKKO**

### sugijakkoboy@gmail.com | boysugi20.github.io

### **ABOUT ME**

A dedicated, hardworking, responsible, and loyal individual with 3 years of experience working, developing, and maintaining web applications as a System Analyst. Committed to continuous learning and professional development with a passion for technology. Keen on sharing knowledge and best practices with colleagues.

### **EXPERIENCE**

#### OCT 2022 - PRESENT

## SENIOR SYSTEM ANALYST, BINA NUSANTARA IT DIVISION

- Enhance and maintain an application used to support online and onsite examination process in Bina Nusantara University.
- Enhance and maintain an application used to support student grading process in Bina Nusantara University.
- Resolve technical difficulties encountered by students and staff during examinations.
- Collaborate with programmers to develop API used in applications.
- Manage application development and enhancement timeline.
- Optimize existing applications to improve user experience and reduce system load.
- Provide documentation (Data Flow Diagram, Entity Relationship Diagram, and Deployment Documents)

## OCT 2021 - OCT 2022

### SYSTEM ANALYST, BINA NUSANTARA IT DIVISION

- Develop and maintain an application used to control access to Bina Nusantara University campuses in response to the COVID-19 pandemic.
- Maintain an application used to support online examination process in Bina Nusantara University.
- Debug, fix, and enhance SQL Stored Procedures used in application to fetch data from database
- Analyze requirements based on user needs.
- Collaborate with programmers to develop new features on existing applications.
- Collaborate with programmers to enhance applications to fit new user needs.
- Trace errors caused by incorrect data on database.

#### MAR 2020 - OCT 2021

## JUNIOR SYSTEM ANALYST, BINA NUSANTARA IT DIVISION

- Assist seniors on solving application errors.
- Assist users with problems on application usage.
- Assist seniors in maintaining an application used to support online examination process in Bina Nusantara University.
- Collaborate with programmers to debug applications.

## **EDUCATION**

## JUN 2022 - PRESENT

## MA IN COMPUTER SCIENCE, BINA NUSANTARA UNIVERSITY (3.9 GPA)

**Thesis title**: "Lightweight Face Recognition-Based Portable Attendance System With Liveness Detection"

## **SEP 2018 – JUN 2022**

# BA IN COMPUTER SCIENCE, BINA NUSANTARA UNIVERSITY (3.74 GPA)

**Thesis title**: "Masked Face Recognition for a Lightweight School Attendance Management System during COVID-19 Pandemic"

## **SKILLS**

- SQL
- Python
- Machine Learning
- Computer Vision
- Django
- Flask

- Docker
- Information Technology
- System Testing
- System Analysis
- Analytical Skills
- Internet of Things